

Graphic Designer Gabrielle Sinclair

Contact: Gabrielsnclr@gmail.com

Profile

I am a self-motivated, and creative problem solver. I love to communicate ideas and spread good emotions. I am always learning and open to new experiences.

Design tools

- \blacksquare PS + AI + AD + AP
- HTML + CSS + Sass
- Figma + XD

Personal skills

- Drawing
- Painting
- Baking
- Carpentry

Soft skills

- Organization
- Resourceful learner
- Time management
- Detail oriented

Portfolio link

Relevant Work Experience

Client

Fairy P logo project: Sep. 2020 — Oct. 2020

The client was in need of a logo to use for the branding of their online business and social media. I was tasked to create a logo using a reference from a personal drawing.

A I designed a personal brand to represent the client's personality and ideals with a mascot vector logo. I generated the brand color scheme and font as well.

I attracted more customers to the client's business and social media, it increased 40%; drawn to the client by the brand's unique and authentic style.

Client

West Palm Management group logo: Sep. 2019 — Oct. 2019

A client was in need of a logo for their new real estate management business, started in west palm beach, FL. I was tasked to create an appropriate logo mark.

I learned about consumer interests and dislikes in the real estate industry. I created a minimalist home styled logo for the company, after multiple iterations.

The client was satisfied with their mark and they successfully attained prosperous real estate clients in NY and Chicago: amounted to over \$100,000.

Graduate Case Study

Paws for Orlando style guide: Mar. 2019 — Apr. 2019

My team and I were assigned to create an organization that operated for the economy or general community. We were tasked to create the brand identity.

I was a member of the graphic design team. We created assets for the website layout for the UX/UI team and designed the entire brand style guide.

Our marketing project was presented among our community and effectively connected to the pseudo-client's target audience.

Education

University of Central FloridaBA in Web Design and Digital media
2017—2020

Valencia College Associates degree in Arts 2015—2017